Daughter, the path has not always been easy but you have never faltered.
Filha, embora o caminho nem sempre seja fácil, você jamais fraquejou.
Ours is a journey that spans generations. Where one story ends,
A nossa jornada abrange gerações. Onde uma história termina,
another begins...
outra começa...
The world our ancestors faced was brutal...
O mundo dos nossos ancestrais era brutal...
...yet from it they drew life.
Mesmo assim, dele, extraiu-se vida.
And though the road to prosperity was at times harsh...
E apesar do caminho para a prosperidade ter sido árduo...
From it great civilizations arose...
Dele, sugiram grandes civilizações...
As well as those who would oppose them.
E também os que se oporiam a elas.
With dreams of conquest of their own.
Com seus próprios ideais de conquista.
Creating mighty empires.
Criando impérios poderosos.
If only to see them fall.
Mesmo que viessem a cair.
Yet from the ashes of the old, new possibilities arise...
Mas, das antigas cinzas, novas possibilidades surgem...
You need only persevere.
Basta perseverar.
For united mankind is capable of many things.
Pois a humanidade unida é capaz de muitas coisas.
Both great...
Tanto boas...
And terrible.
Quanto más.
Still, the true power to shape this world has always lain in your hands.
Ainda assim, o poder de mudar o mundo sempre esteve nas suas mãos.
Choose well.
Escolha bem.
Always.
Sempre.